Chief
We're already here.
Why the pause?
Still planning to lead the way?
I, Zhang Tianyou, always finish what I start.
If some matters aren't resolved,
I won't have peace even if I go inside.
What else do you want to know?
When my father led the Dragon-Seeking Zhang Family here back then,
what exactly did they encounter in this tomb
that got them completely wiped out?
They were attacked by evil creatures.
The four great families fought desperately to escape with their lives.
How's that for an ending?
Since we share a bond forged in battle,
then why are you pointing a gun at me now?
Whatever old scores you want to settle,
now that the Tidal Tomb has been found,
your time as Chief is up.
Patriarch Mei,
I went to great lengths to gather the Talisman, Curse, Seal, and Eye,
just to help us find this tomb
and open it.
But do you really know how to break through its traps?
Aren't you afraid the guys in this tomb
might follow you back to solve the mystery?
Don't try to bluff me again.
It's that thing!
It's awake!
Run!
After him!
Sister Mei,
you said they'd definitely succeed,
right?
Sister Mei?
Where are they?
They were just here.
Ling Yu!
You damn...
Let go!
Let go of Ling Yu!
Ling Yu!
Qi Tianting!
Look at the state you're in now.
There's no point in living, is there?
Let me put you out of your misery.
It's the unique token of the Dragon-Seeking Zhang Family.
They all perished here.
These things could buy half the Shanghai Bund, right?
I'll just pocket some first.
Wait a minute.
These jewels are laced with a neurotoxin refined by ancient methods.
Touching it induces a feeling of extreme euphoria.
Until you finally die of exhaustion in that ecstasy.
Fenglin, there's a door here.
Once this curse is lifted,
this immense wealth will go to our Mei and Wan families.
Wealth is great,
but without Zhang Tianyou's help,
how do we break into the tomb and suppress the evil?
Don't worry, he won't get away.
When the time comes, with a gun to his head,
he'll do it whether he wants to or not.
Fenglin, let's go.
Fenglin, come on!
Fenglin!
Mei Yuanhe!
What are you doing?
I did it!
I am now the Shanghai Bund's...
Get lost!
No...
I am Huaxia's...
I am the richest man in Huaxia!
Wan Fenglin!
You've gone mad!
Righteous power of heaven and earth, enter my body; Dragon-seeking spell, suppress the root of poison.
What exactly is going on here?
The Celestial Seal, forged from meteorite iron,
has a crystal magnetic core at its center.
It can disrupt biological magnetic fields.
The scent it emits
can even affect the activity of some venomous creatures.
That's also why
it can control the Mei family's Five Venomous Creatures.
That's amazing!
Let me take a look.
This is a divine artifact from the heavens!
So why did you think I
tried so hard to gather the Talisman, Curse, Seal, and Eye?
Without any one of them,
we wouldn't be able to get out of here alive.
Let's go.
Then what do the other two do?
They're passes to buy our way through.
Hurry.
What a pity.
Zhang Tianyou
Enemies are bound to cross paths.
Go to hell!
Ling Yu, Chun'er!
Stay hidden and don't move!
This bastard treats you pretty well.
Jiushuang, you're familiar with the tomb's layout.
Take them back the way we came.
What about you?
I need to handle the rest on my own.
Don't follow me.
Zhang Tianyou, I'm going with you.
Me too.
No.
Leng Feiyan's Sand-Turning Gang will meet you outside.
If you come with me,
you'll only be a burden.
and distract me.
Fine.
Then just stay out of this.
Then... can I go?
You can come along.
Let's go.
This is handy.
To see the true god,
an offering is required.
Screw your offering!
Li Xiao.
I suggest you calm down.
These two seem to have quite a temper.
Bullshit!
What the hell are these things?
I already told you.
You didn't believe me.
Young Master, w-what...
What is going on here?
These two are gatekeepers,
called Hanging Puppets.
Suspended by Heavenly Silkworm Thread,
they are incredibly tough.
See the two grooves on the door?
Those are two keyholes.
Brute force won't work.
We have to use this.
Would they even recognize this?
These two talisman books are made of special Yin-Yang Wood.
Under special conditions, their wood pulp
can emit bioelectric waves.
Their ink is mixed with Meteorite Sand,
which has a weak magnetic field.
They're not meant to be read.
Move. Move aside.
They're used to match frequencies.
Just like the key to a safe.
Impossible.
You can't be this powerful.
A pass to clear the way.
Get it now?
Knowledge is the best key.
Violence only triggers more violent defense mechanisms.